---
header:
  lang: en
  slug: /about
  title: "About Us"
  desc: "ما می‌خواهیم به تیم‌های سراسر دنیا کمک کنیم با همکاری آسان‌تر به بهره‌وری بیشتر برسند. با تیم ما بیشتر آشنا شوید."
body:
  header: "Coolest Developers Of All Times"
  team:
    -
      name: "Farhad Hedayatfard "
      jobTitle: "Founder & CEO"
      twitter: "https://twitter.com/farhad_hf"
      linkedin: "https://ir.linkedin.com/in/fhedayatifard"
      front: "farhad-front"
      back: "farhad-back"
    -
      name: "Kazem Keshavarz"
      jobTitle: "Founder & CTO"
      twitter: "https://twitter.com/_otik"
      linkedin: "https://ir.linkedin.com/in/keykakito"
      front: "kazem-front"
      back: "kazem-back"
    -
      name: "Homayoun Hedayatfard"
      jobTitle: "Product Engineer"
      twitter: "https://twitter.com/hmn_hf"
      linkedin: "https://ir.linkedin.com/in/hmnhf"
      front: "homayoun-front"
      back: "homayoun-back"
    -
      name: "Azadeh Nourbakhsh"
      jobTitle: "Customer Success Manager"
      twitter: "https://twitter.com/azazadeh"
      linkedin: "https://ir.linkedin.com/in/azadehnourbakhsh"
      front: "azadeh-front"
      back: "azadeh-back"
    -
      name: "Sina Sabbagh"
      jobTitle: "Marketing Manager"
      twitter: "https://twitter.com/sinasabbagh"
      linkedin: "https://ir.linkedin.com/in/sina-sabbagh-b566b896"
      front: "sina-front"
      back: "sina-back"
    -
      name: "Roozbeh Mirzaee"
      jobTitle: "Business Development"
      linkedin: "https://www.linkedin.com/in/roozbeh-mirzaee-97810812a"
      front: "roozbeh-front"
      back: "roozbeh-back"
    -
      name: "Amirhossein Aghdasi"
      jobTitle: "Business Development"
      twitter:
      linkedin:
      front: "amirhossein-front"
      back: "amirhossein-back"
    -
      name: "Ali Fazaeli"
      jobTitle: "Product Manager"
      twitter:
      linkedin:
      front: "ali-front"
      back: "ali-back"
    -
      name: "Amirali Sariaslani"
      jobTitle: "Marketing Expert"
      twitter:
      linkedin:
      front: "amirali-front"
      back: "amirali-back"
    -
      name: "Negar Goljan"
      jobTitle: "Sales Expert"
      twitter:
      linkedin:
      front: "negar-front"
      back: "negar-back"
    -
      name: "Mehrdad Asadi"
      jobTitle: "Customer Success Expert"
      twitter:
      linkedin:
      front: "mehrdad-front"
      back: "mehrdad-back"
    -
      name: "Mehrdad Mohammadi"
      jobTitle: "Customer Success Expert"
      twitter:
      linkedin:
      front: "mehrdad-front"
      back: "mehrdad-back"
    -
      name: "Bilbo"
      jobTitle: "Meh!"
      front: "bilbo-front"
      back: "bilbo-back"
  mission:
    header: "Who are we and What are we doing?"
    body: |
      We think that collaboration is the ultimate solution for building high performance teams.<br/><br/>
      Our goal is to help teams all over the world collaborate easier and increase their performance and efficiency.<br/><br/>
      We really like building great products. We love the web and the internet, and luckily for us, the internet is one of the best platforms for building collaborations tools.
...
